

HAKIM MASZELAN

ASPIRING DATA ANALYST

DATE OF BIRTH: 9TH FEBRUARY 1995

EMAIL: hakim135xz@gmail.com

CONTACT: +6013-2566771

PROFILE

A passionate engineer majored in Mechanical Engineering that is willing to dedicate my youth to expand my horizons. Possess the ability to make data driven decisions, to be able to operate within a team efficiently and the passion to enter the data analyst field. Has obtained Python 3 and Data Analytics Certification from Codecademy.

EDUCATION

Taylor's Lakeside University 2015-2019

Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering

INTEC Education College 2013-2015

Foundation in Science and Engineering

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in Python 3 coding language and data analysis.
- Proficient in extracting and analyzing data with SQL.
- Proficient with Python 3 data analysis modules eg. Seaborn.
- Adept with Statistics Applied Mathematics.
- Proficient with 3D and 2D CAD modelling and simulations.

LANGUANGES

CERTIFICATIONS

Python 3 and Data Analytics Course

Learning and using Python 3 an interpreted, object-oriented, high-level programming language and Data Management using SQL with dynamic semantics for use with Data analytics, Data science, Web Developments, Machine Learning, Al and Mobile App Developments.

UNIVERSITY PROJECT

Final Year Project 2019

Developing and coding a program with MATLAB as an alternative fluid flow simulation.

Taylor's Engineering Project 2018

Designing and Fabricating Human Powered Vehicle

Taylor's Engineering Project 2017

Designing and Fabricating Reusable Archery Target- 3rd Place winner

Taylor's Engineering Project 2016

- Designing and Fabricating Lightweight HPV chasis

SOFTWARE SKILLS

SOLIDWORKS

Phyton

SQL

AutoCAD

ANSYS

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Internship Program Ram-Bytes SDN BHD Jan 2018-March 2018

- Involved in the upgrade of vibration monitoring system, BN3500 in Ultilities Kerteh and Gebeng for Petronas Gas Berhad.
- Factory Acceptance Test (FAT).
- Operation and Maintainence BN3500 Training by General Electrics.
- System 1 EVO training by General Electrics.
- Lighting support fabrication for upstream and downstream.
- Petronas site visit.

HLA ASSOCIATES SDN BHD (August 2019-April 2022)

- 1. Proposed of Chiller System and BAS System Replacement at Bank Pembangunan Malaysia Berhad.
 - Assist in designing a new chiller and cooling tower to replace and upgrade the existing system.
- 2. Improvement of Existing Air-Conditioning and Mechanical Ventilation (ACMV) Systems and its Associated Works at KL International Airport, Sepang, Selangor.
 - Study the existing design of the ACMV system in KLIA and proposing a new upgraded system to replace the old design.
- 3. Booster Pump, 2.5 Million Liters Water Tank, Flowmeter Testing and Commissioning in Kg Alai (Ranhill SAJ)
 - Testing and commissioning water tank, centrifugal pumps (Pump Performance Test) to ensure that the system was able to perform according to specifications.
- 4. Upgrading of "Sekolah Menengah Vokasional Setapak" to "Kolej Vokasional Setapak Kuala Lumpur".
 - Assist in designing the mechanical and electrical system including ACMV, Fire Protection, Plumbing and Sanitation system.
- 5. Cadangan Membina Skim Bekalan Air Baru di Wilayah Iskandar
 - Assist in designing the FM200 fire protection system and other related mechanical services.
- 6. HLA Associates Sdn Bhd Quality Management System (ISO) Internal Auditor.
 - Joining the auditing committee in HLA Associates.
- 7. Air Selangor Dam Safety Inspection.
 - Assist in safety inspection of 7 dams in Klang Valley by inspecting the existing mechanical and electrical system for the dams.
- 8.VRF/VRV, Chiller and Cooling Tower, ACMV Design for Building and Services
 - Tender out ACMV designs for HLA Associates Sdn Bhd to multiple projects.
- 9. Plumbing and Sanitation System for Building and Services
 - o Tender out Plumbing and Sanitation System design for HLA Associates Sdn Bhd.
- 10. Pembinaan Baraj Baru di Rantau Panjang, Sungai Muda, Seberang Perai Utara, Pulau Pinang.
 - Design upgrading works for existing pumping scheme.
- 11. Projek Skim Pemindahan Air Jeniang, Kedah (Phase 1) Ampang Jajar dan Muka Sauk di Sungai Muda Daerah Sik, Kedah.
- 12. CAPEX 21 Refurbishment and Upgrading works for 6 WTPs in Selangor for Air Selangor
- 13. CA 21 Study of 8 existing WTPs in Selangor for the purpose of refurbishment and upgrading works.

Ripe Fresh Sdn Bhd (April 2022-Now)

- Working as a Mechanical Design Engineer for a startup company creating farming system indoors using aeroponics and hydroponics technology.
- Handling household and industrial farming system design and manufacturing.
- Handling design improvement works, fabrication process and supply and delivery chain.
- Handling procurement for system fabrication, maintenance and improvements.
- Handling installation of system at site.